<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CS 315 Student List: 2022</string>
    <string name="placeholderName">Names go HERE</string>
    <string name="rwt_name">Rich Tanner</string>
    <string name="rwt_title">Clinical Professor of DET</string>
    <string name="rwt_title_bar">Prof Tanner String</string>



    <string name="bmb_name">Benjamin Blackmon</string>
    <string name="bmb_title">Senior DET Major</string>
    <string name="bmb_title_bar">Benjamin\'s App Ideas</string>
    <string name="bmb_list_maker_title_bar">List Maker</string>
    <string name="bmb_list_maker_description">
        List Maker is a super customizable list creator.
        There will be one main view where you can add "categories" to it. A category can have another category added to it,
        or a list. A list is comprised of a bunch of smaller items that can be given a priority,
        a date, and have reminders set on it for notifications. The main view can have categories and lists added to it
        so you can see only lists in the category for "school", or perhaps only one list for when you go shopping.
        This is to get the best parts of the inheritance system (where we can store categories and lists inside of other
        categories for organizational purposes), while also being able to show multiple lists at the same time (say,
        multiple classes for school). The items shown in the main view can be sorted by priority, due date, reminder date,
        or alphabetically (and any other types of sorting things that might be helpful.
    </string>

    <string name="bmb_rpg_life_title_bar">RPG Life</string>
    <string name="bmb_rpg_life_description">
        RPG Life is an app about taking real life progress and turning it into something more quantifiable.
        Users will be able to add types of work and prescribe it to a particular stat (strength, intelligence,
        dexterity, etc.). This will improve their stats and they will be able to have numbers to display actual growth
        to motivate people for their progress.
    </string>
</resources>