<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">CS 315 Student List: 2022</string>
    <string name="placeholderName">Names go HERE</string>
    <string name="rwt_name">Rich Tanner</string>
    <string name="rwt_title">Clinical Professor of DET</string>
    <string name="rwt_title_bar">Prof Tanner String</string>
    <string name="acd_name">Alissa Davis</string>
    <string name="acd_tempsugg_text">Random Prompt Generator</string>
    <string name="acd_tempsugg_det">Generate prompts for AI...</string>
    <string-array name="acd_app_suggestions">
        <item>DND Dice Tower</item>
        <item>Habit Checklist</item>
        <item>Grade Checker Widget</item>
        <item>Random Prompt Generator</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="acd_appsugg_desc">
        <item>Roll an array of dice...</item>
        <item>Build good daily habits...</item>
        <item>Check your grades...</item>
        <item>Generate prompts for AI...</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="acd_appsugg_moreinfo">
        <item>The user gets to select a type of dice and then roll it to get a result. It is very helpful for people who play DnD games or those who rely on chance to make decisions.</item>
        <item>The user makes daily habits they want to develop. They can set reminders to remind themself to check the habit off their list for the day. The list resets at midnight in their local time.</item>
        <item>This widget allows users to check their grades on their home screen without having to open their school app.</item>
        <item>This app allows users to generate random prompts from a dictionary to use for AI generators (for instance, Dall-E image generator).</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="agm_name">Anthony Moncivais</string>
    <string name="agm_title">CS and DET Student at ACU</string>
    <string name="lvlup_title">Lvl Up</string>
    <string name="lvlup_description">   An app to track things such as workouts, studying, diet etc... and provides players with a stats sheet just like those that can be found in RPGs. The idea is to get people that would normally invest a lot of time on leveling up a virtual character to spend some time leveling themselves up</string>
    <string name="church_geolocator_title"> Church Geolocator</string>
    <string name="church_geolocator_description"> An app to search the area around you to find churches in the area and provide you with basic information to get connected</string>

    <!-- ncm strings -->
    <string name="ncm_name">Noah Massie</string>
    <string name="ncm_title">Senior Student of DET</string>
    <string name="ncm_title_bar">Noah Massie Info</string>
    <string name="ncm_app_title">Mythos Tree</string>
    <string name="ncm_app_ideas">App Possibilities</string>
    <string name="ncm_app_info">Interactive Mythological Tree which allows you to select a pantheon and then learn which gods were supposed to affect which aspects of life such as love, agriculture, war, and so on, while also providing their family trees and possibly the backgrounds/origins of the individual gods.</string>

    <!--blk strings -->
    <string name="blk_name">Bailey Kimmel</string>
    <string name="description">Elle Woods but Computer Science</string>
    <string name="nails">Abilene alone has over 30 nail bars. This proposes an issue women face: Which one has the shortest wait?</string>
    <string name="title_bk">NailTime would allow nail bars to post their wait times which would clear waiting rooms, boost business, and accommodate the customer. </string>
    <string name="MM_title_bar">Marlon Eduardo Miller</string>
    <string name="MM_appTitle_bar">Risky World Accounting</string>
    <string name="MM_RW_1">The Risky World App is an Accounting Website idea, designed by my father and developed by me, is a accounting database system keeping track of general information, parameters, catalogs, and users from different departments inside a company from Honduras.</string>
    <string name="MM_RW_2">This app is fully dynamic, where administrators can add, delete or change information constantly by accessing their accounts, modifying records and assigning tasks to several other administrators and users.
</string>
    <string name="MM_RW_3">Risky World is an accountability prototype system architecture designed to implement basic security to several roles for users, implement basic parameters and functionalities in the applications, building registration, wholesale in accounting items and a clean and integral financial status for the company.</string>
    <string name="MJ_Title">MDog\'s Incrediblely Bad Ideas</string>
    <string name="MJ_Text">I wanted to elaborate more on the apps I thought about creating. The inventors app is an app where inventors can post new ideas and request funds, material, and assistance. The Snack Raid app is an app that keeps track of the snackage in your house and has a randomizer if you dont know what to snack on. Lastly, have you ever wanted to capatilize..I mean spread the new online age of dating? Why spend over a hundred dollars on a cheap bluetooth LED when you can spend 1 dollar on a cheap piece of software! With Couple Buttons, you can now instagate (that means start) conversations with your partner. Simply register thier phone number as well as your own, create your buttons, and chat with the ease of a simple push.</string>
</resources>